right um well this is weird as everyone
said
but um so this has to be an hour long
um you might see some horses and welcome
to Yorkshire a lovely land of green but
um sir I have to talk about myself
and I forgot to read the prompts but I
know someone wants to know one question
is what annoys me and what annoys me is
well first of all
it is the subjective fi it's the sub
it's kind of like a random attachment to
anything and everything kind of like uh
I don't know what it is but it could be
like a buffer for like um for instance
if we had no values or No Boundaries
then it would essentially be
um they've been a trespassing everyone
can go everywhere so these like kind of
buffer bumps
um on random things that they attach the
emotions to allows us
to know that allows us to assess things
and also like in every aspect you know
but anyway
um what annoys me is um I suppose
random sounds like random tapping sounds
um
oh just sloppiness you know it's like
people who are sloppy I also hate
I don't like it when someone can't laugh
at themselves
or lying hate lying
um
yeah I don't know well this is oh it's
only been a minute I was like [\h__\h]
there's a 60 more minutes to go
um
but yeah I don't like lying I don't like
I don't know I was gonna say dishonestly
but that's the same thing but
I have not done any introspection on
this I'll just see is what you get I was
like well just randomly go on a walk at
5am and do a video there here I am
um
yeah
I don't know really I don't really know
what annoys me
um
laziness laziness if like
their attitude to something you know if
they don't want to make it in Life or
just sloppiness and
things like that it's just
brings everyone else down ruins the day
you know of course everyone's got
reasons for their values you know
I think mbti and Ops is like diluted
myself and my views it's
you know it's uh also I'm not
trespassing
because it doesn't exist here it's not
illegal to trespass in the UK if they
only ask you to leave then you've got to
leave and then it's trespassing
um but there's a lot of like open
Pathways where you're allowed to walk
through
England and you're allowed to Camp any
way you want
um because you're free to roam
essentially you know
because Bill Gates is open you know what
he's doing getting all the land but um
yeah
but yeah um
okay so I don't know what you want from
me question wise someone said to go off
the script or like talk naturally
but like well I can remember some of
them from watching other people's videos
but they're like you know what do you
think the biggest problem in society is
well obviously the standard of like
we've been
I don't know if it's happened naturally
or the te Doms have just like
systematized everyone into these like
Ultra like boxed off you know boxed off
into our little metal walls um
to get the most work out of course we're
slaves of course we're an ant colony
that's our existence bacteria on the
globe you know got to spread we're
indifferent to the spores on your ass
you know that's just obvious but
you know the biggest problem
I'd say is that where we don't know
we're on the crack and we don't know
what's exactly going to follow up from
our Rampages from the sun's it's an
awful position but we don't know what's
going on with the rampaging
this this crack that was still hooked on
like more and more and more like you
know Non-Stop and the like for instance
I think about if you went to Mars you
know we get to Mars and we can't leave
the atmosphere it's like kind of Trapped
in a building that's where it's heading
you know the police says and and that
sounds like control you know EP control
but I don't think it is it's more or
less like
we're built for um so like think about
Aegis and EPS or like you know the peas
versus the JS the ois like a uh a bread
or a string and a tightening and
tightening it naturally and then the EPS
are just unraveling that and the SI
hates that but it allows for new things
to go inside the society you know but
you can't have everything you know
rolling
you can't ever think chaotic but the
ball has to keep rolling for new things
to be added and otherwise we're still in
caves you know like the first like if it
isn't fixed don't break it oh wait so
something's like if it's not broken
don't fix it I'm like oh that that's
stupid it's so stupid like
it's so oh God
yeah I mean it's like okay Mindy go in
the cave and eat your own [\h__\h] you know
smear it on the walls yes that's
essentially what it means to me
Rejuvenation backwards
um
what else do I say
I don't know there's horses but I don't
know if you see them
about five minutes through almost done I
hope no one walks past me because that's
so strange I have to say hi as well you
have to look them in the eyes is it a up
you know
God not it's rude
um
but you're microanalyzing everything I
say lovely
I don't really know what to say I should
have read the script but I didn't um
right um
what was it oh like a troubling sometime
right this feels like
entering like the Marina Trench like it
doesn't feel like it right now but when
I was thinking about
talking about my emotions or like a dark
time it's kind of like invalidating of
myself in that I'm not going to share
everything of my trauma
and I can't share all of the everyone's
got trauma obviously everybody even when
they don't but I know that's kind of
like oh how invalidating but it's kind
of like some people just don't have
trauma if you level it up on the scales
and it's like this little Syrian girl
selling her kidneys and is a prostitute
sold off to a man and then you've got
this like Ultra like you know like this
Rich of course we're rich as well if you
earn if you earn over 25 here annually
you're in the top one percent globally
you know Jesus like where the utopians
living on the dystopians you know of
course we've gotta I have to apply my
fence but of course you have to view it
your Society is [\h__\h] otherwise nothing
changes you can't just go this is lovely
and then nothing will actually get done
um
but yeah um
there's cows so you might hear a moving
a coup but um
forgot what I was saying
um
I don't know what I was saying but I was
talking something about
um
there's people
um what was it talking about
[\h__\h]
I think I was talking about
the
something about capitalism or like
you can't
I feel like I'm just sharing everything
I've sleep process done and it's only
seven minutes
seven minutes oh God but um
let's walk for the corn wheat field
I don't know the way out I don't think
there was a way out because it's like
it's the end of the city but it's weird
because the city's divided and there's
like a farm don't buy a building in the
middle
um actually I think it's that way
yeah it's that way
anyway wheat
but um
yeah I don't know what I was saying and
obviously you're probably thinking oh
that's playing his channel changing he
doesn't remember like
is it that simple could I be lying you
know could I be could I know Ops so much
that I want I could be a psychopath
and I want to be presented a certain way
you know that I might [\h__\h] myself up
um
I cannot remember what I was talking
about
um
at all
it's very warm
but you know when you like try and
convert Fahrenheit to Celsius because
I'm assuming you're Americans oh sorry
Linda hello hello Noel oh Lord and Mike
were watching too sign if you're
watching thank you thank you
still want to know what language you
speak though
anyway
um
if you're wondering who these people are
well we're the heart of the group The
Ops group we are the core
and if people know about it God you I'm
probably known as a racist but you don't
know my life story and that I grew up
around
I did the it's like that's why I think
I'm not I'm that's why I think I'm
immune to it these are my people these I
don't see them as any different so I can
mock them because I don't view them I
see them as my brother brothers like
you know why would I treat them any
different from what I would another
person a mocking like
like attributes but they're the one of
the same you know
I didn't look at them and go oh they're
different okay well yeah I'm pointing
out the differences
but that's to me that's like where
equals you know
like
I'm not treating them different but yeah
it's a tractor
and oh 10 minutes lovely 50 more minutes
to go
um let's talk about some lags shall we
maybe I'll remember what I was talking
about I really can't remember and it's
so annoying
um
what is it like I think one of them was
like where do you want to be in five
years
well
I've always wanted to
we'll run a business it was always
business
when I was um nine I would go around
knocking on people's doors and like
wanting for them to donate to charity
um and there is like 70 quid
um for like cancer research rspca which
is like a
like animal protection protection thing
um
but yeah oh you know the saddest thing
okay let's go into the trench the
saddest thing one of the saddest things
death oh my God my cat
I can't even give the full oh this is
what I was talking about I can't give
the full pill I can't give the full meal
because if I do it's cut right this is
why I find it invalidating of my own
trauma is that if I give I don't
obviously No One's Gonna Give the entire
[\h__\h] it's like think about a house
and the hoarders and it's like you're
telling someone I'm a bit of a hoarder
like oh let me help you you let them in
the hallway
and then they're like oh this is scruffy
we can clean it's like yeah you're gonna
let you know if you want to You're Gonna
help
let them clean it with you and then
you're not gonna let them in the other
door you know and then they could want
to go and leave a donga well why weren't
you and then they'll suspect some things
up
so it's like
I don't want to and it's invalidating
because you're if I'm saying I've got a
hoarding problem
and then I only show the little space
it's like that's hoarding it's kind of
and also I feel like if I drop the bomb
into a space essentially I've and not it
kind of sounds fi like my values are the
worst of course they're not the west but
in my view pretty [\h__\h] up I'm not
gonna list them
but um
you know like placing that there it's
kind of like I assume that no one can
talk about anything else
in the I've now lowered like the economy
think about everything's fine and I've
just dropped it and deflated everything
and now it's like [\h__\h] I can't even
bring my emotions
because um it's not worth anything
anymore I can't get anything with this
currency
um you know I mean like uh I can't
they won't be able to say something
um because it's kind of like well that's
nothing in comparison what he just said
you know kind of thing obviously other
people going through worse but it's just
that's what it is and it's invalidating
because I can't I wouldn't share the
whole thing
and then it's kind of like is that it
you know it's like oh
and it's just so I don't I thought that
was gonna feel very like you know
like enshrined within it like I'm
sharing this
oh you know the film not the film but
like you know my American Dad and it's
the golden turd or like Family Guy or
something like that and he's like kills
his [\h__\h] wife for this Tad it's like
no one can have it all
it's kind of like that I'm revealing the
turd the golden turd
um we got a lake this is an education
this is called a back which is a slow
running stream
um yeah the feels of wheat blowing the
wind
[Music]
it's really nice we get like 20 hour
days in summer
it's just lovely it's it [\h__\h] up if you
sleep though
really does
um
but yeah it's nice it's nice we live as
high as Alaska
um
but yes and that we get we get nice cool
Winters
because um the Gulf Stream
but yeah
I don't really know what to talk about
I wonder if you're going to fizzy or not
when you're like oh look if I is the
Little Harp and you know
these other things oh Gabriel's probably
watching this hello ola
if not gonna send it to the cognitive I
don't know what you're called I'm so
sorry I didn't even look into you
I blindly walked into it
um but yeah this is a [\h__\h] show
but I've got
45 minutes to correct it so let's see
um
my mouth's dry
it's a head of coffee and I knew I would
so I drank have you ever done that you
know you go to the tap like the faucet
and you just like you always like as a
kid you know you just run you'll be burn
dry you know you just be exhausted like
patching like a little African Child in
the hot desert sun an Ethiopian and then
you just it feels so good you know it
feels so nice and then it stops and it's
kind of like sometimes you'll want to
drink slower so then it doesn't actually
like take away the joyous quick but then
it doesn't work it's like oh I could
have been gulping but anyway
yeah
um there's people
other flock
but yeah um well I could talk about
interest I really like languages
I really like um
oh it's just it's a kind of shallow
reason that it's like oh
I look very smart in front of other
people but yeah it's kind of like it's
very very shallow it's sad but as I say
you know this we're slaves so
gotta get the chemicals on board from
when you can get them
um
so I don't really know what to say or
what to share to you guys like obviously
gonna be thinking oh look play a blast
consume or sleep last year like that I
think that's pretty obvious like I'm not
no trouble speaking you know
um
yeah
I hope my battery doesn't die as well
but
um well
I don't know really I didn't really know
what to talk about
you know but I know that I'm very
right okay so I think that right other
people think I would decide uh Observer
and I think it's because I've very much
oh God when you're in the same Arena
you can't not see your own patterns and
it's like
God if I oh my God like
the f i within me oh my God I just I do
feel I'm blind to it
like but it's not right right think
about this it's not like I'm blind
I'm still blind to it but if you've got
like a it's like a ball and you put
water around it and it's like uncovering
this like thing but you can't see it but
you're where it's existing around it
like GTA you know like um you're going
on the map you go around the um the
black spot you like it I know it's there
I don't know how big it is so I'm
assuming this is what it is but you know
I mean like kind of like that
but um sensory
I don't know I kind of Mock and look at
um you know EPS whatever they're called
as well stupid
um
also right controversial but um
well I don't know how it actually sprung
this is very nice
I hope there's no one down there
isn't that lovely
dry
three as we see
but um
yeah oh my God Hemlock Hemlock I ate
Hemlock I didn't know it was poisonous I
was on a hike and I was like eating all
the random plants I was like oh yes
nature anything's organic and pure
absorb the surroundings and it felt like
my brain had was like a pot of jelly but
like it was stuck to the top it was oh
my God I just assumed it was the 30 mile
hike you know
and then I hit some Quavers which is
like is they look curly
um crisps
um and then drink lots of water and it
was very I felt fine afterwards
so I don't know what they're talking
about like you'll die and I'm like no
but I get the flowers I think
so it's okay
um I'm probably ruining the nation's
crops
um but the the biggest problems to say
is like obviously mixing people but even
in itself we've kind of gone obviously
you can't have a species that believes
it should kill itself you know
self-destruct but you'll see in the west
a lot of people want to be childless is
it kind of like you know you've got a
power structure at the top and it sounds
a bit like the patriarchy but obviously
different different
of course it's special
um
and it's like the redistribution because
you'll have
the royal family for instance a lot of
males and then poorer people will have a
lot of females and then they marry up
and down you know I forgot the word for
it her higher micro mini or something
like that
um
so yeah there's that which is like this
slow stream redistributing things
and um and is that what our society is
doing this power through like we know
like morals were like
saying like oh but no like the um sexism
and like you know homophobia and like
racism all that from the other like
cultures we didn't know if that's right
or wrong we don't know if women should
be working around men can we know the
sexual harassments is it should we just
not have men around women should we just
have it separate it's like oh that's
sexism it's like oh but it's stopping
animalistic edges you know like
yeah and that's where Free Will comes in
anyone can kill someone anyone can rip
and murder someone in the right
environment anyone can
you know we've all been somewhere where
we've just lost it and just lost the
plot
and you know we're like whoa what the
[\h__\h] was like Jesus and I had that in me
yeah probably thinking like oh no that's
just a youth thing but we have the
look at these grains so pretty
um
but yeah
back in the Sun
but yeah I like languages I like
oh but you know the like the biggest
pains
like oh it's so much admiration
and I've kind of
looking love a little tunnel
Jesus spooky
um like admirations
I kind of um I lost that
after a big corruptive period it was
like five years ago you know but
yeah I don't know if even like sometimes
like every year I'm like wow I can see
so much more
um geez I have to hunt I'm like six foot
six so this is awkward as [\h__\h]
um but yeah
oh lovely it's a bit rumbly
the ground's finally dried though
because it's usually soggy
for a while
um over 20 minutes through
I've already made it to the next town
that's annoying
cause I can't walk around people you
know like talking
about this does that look really weird
it's just over there if you can see I
don't know if you can see the church the
Kirk
um
Jesus you see the houses
looks like a slave plantation
but yeah like um
but yeah like there's these gaps I think
this lag is delayed it's like and it's
kind of like who else is like this who
else is like trapped
in this mind you know of like
I don't know it's just oh there's
horseshoes in here
I don't know really it's just that's
what I'm saying like why
why would I invalidate my own
um traumas when I you know I'm not gonna
no one would no one would like seriously
you know you've got to be a bit like
it's selfish in a way isn't it you know
because you're kind of throwing this on
someone you just don't do that you know
in my opinion
but yeah the missing
I don't know this is so [\h__\h] and crappy
and I didn't plan anything and that's
that's why you know oh there's a dog
that's awkward
it's kind of like is he talking to
someone
obviously not
yeah
thank you
all right okay
but yeah like um
hard
I don't know what was going to say
my lips are so dry
you're saying it's white
that's how dry my mouth is
because I had loads of coffee
you'd have probably not want to see that
be all discussed just for good reason
you don't want my jams but it's cooler
like how
embodied with become of Technology you
know like we feel anxious from Reading
comments you know like Scripts
um and we feel
we feel the nervousness and the disgust
from that is actually obviously you know
biological response to keep yourself
safe
um
probably should hold it higher
yeah I thought
it's annoying I kind of wish I was
better at blasting
and keep I don't know I just
I don't know and this is 20 minutes
three minutes through
um
yeah
uh well yeah right I remember so we're
kind of on this high of
you're on this high of capitalism and
just wealth in general and
who decided that we should have the
power to colonize the universe who
decided us you know we're just kind of
taking that in like think about a bit of
moss growing somewhere or a few weeds in
your garden you get too big you pull
them out you know
seriously and the people like aliens
don't exist nope it's like
well why are we here darling why are we
here we're proof of aliens in itself and
then people will say
oh we need proof for that and I'm like
you don't need proof because if you look
the size of the universe look at the
spec that we are it's so stupid to ask
for our own self-marked self-assessed
self-spoken about proof
you know it's better off asking the
squirrels in the tree they probably know
more our size difference is nothing
nothing at all
um
we'll go this way shall we
but yeah I don't
I forgot
oh wait where is it like what do you
want to be okay right that's a good
question I'm on hotels
um
so annoying I found my clones and I want
to do the exact same thing
which is the worst and they're not doing
it because they keep doing other things
and I'm like ah [\h__\h] that's me
and it's good because
yeah it's good but I can't stick to that
I I've always had the vision
to do things
um like I said oh I wanted slushies I
think you call them Slurpees everybody
loves slushies but I had a plan so I
lived near a park and um it was 50 Quid
poons we see 50 pounds and for a slushy
machine and I was gonna get a extension
cords you know
and oh God it won't it went close though
it would have been like
Jesus I'd probably need like I don't
know a quarter of a mile no not a
quarter of a mile but one tenth of a
mile
for the Europeans possibly watching
that's like um
I don't know probably
100 meters yeah 100 meters 100 meters of
cable and I was thinking oh well I'll
lay it on the floor and I was like no
someone will steal it so I was like I'll
put it on the Light lamp post you know
up there and you know tape her up and
string it to the park and put the
slushing machine on and sell slushies
you know get electric and do that
um oh my other biggest regret Bitcoin
Bitcoin I said to my mum I want to
invest my 50 pounds for my birthday on
bitcoin how old was I was like I think I
was like 10 or something
oh my God
and she said it was a waste of money
well it didn't mean to laugh it was
something like it was 16 million today
and I'm like wow Adam in the the richest
youngest millionaire
um that ever lived
um I did my research as well so it
wasn't just like [\h__\h] may have been
just like oh look the ad said this I'm
going to follow could have been that
could have been that
but still
um
yeah I'm glad but I'm glad I have
regrets very glad I have them if we
didn't we'd be blind we'll be living the
very depressed lives because you can't
see them you'd be too late it's like
[\h__\h] you can't do anything about it now
you know
but yeah
um
the biggest hurdle I've gone over my
life there we go
God
there's so many
um I don't really want to say that
because it's just
as I say it's not really like oh I don't
want pity
but it's as if like um not even looking
at the camera look at the beautiful
flowers
but it's just as I say it's invalidating
it's invalidating with myself
to not share the full story and even if
I did share the full story it's like I'm
exposed I'm like oh Jesus why would
anyone
expose themselves like that and I think
that's what the difference between fi
and f e is you know like
they're just so extroverted but I was
like oh also I don't want to be seen as
a bad person that's another thing I've
slept on is that mouth's so dry is I
don't want other people like think about
it if you've been through a traumatic
experience likelihood is you're [\h__\h]
up in your head yourself you know what I
mean so
why would I want to oh yes hello guys
hello oh
really knows as well but why would I be
like broadcasting
if like a [\h__\h] up mind you know or
maybe I already do that myself
um
but yeah so it's like kind of like that
God oh geez not to sound fi but honestly
yeah I don't it's in the top one percent
of something you're probably thinking oh
everybody says that but no seriously
like
that that broke me that that Shackled me
where I'm like
it gave me so much introspection it gave
me so Much Death of like I was so
insensitive to so many people and it was
disgusting like I couldn't see this
missing thing and it's like oh and even
my sister and just the way I treat
everyone around it's like oh it's just
horrible
you know like just the lack of empathy
for people and just stuck in that stupid
way you know just my own emotions and
I'm indebted to my sister oh not okay it
probably sounds like I beat her up it's
nothing like that's what all the abusers
say no but it's nothing like that
obviously like well I'd even mentioned
that you know I mean if it was but Jesus
I just want to make
I just want to make her life as
comfortable as possible because it's
just what she's done oh it's just
horrible you know it's just
you couldn't like and it tears up my
eyes a bit because it's just like
what she's done is just crazy you know
um
she's literally it's just you know I
mean like it's just what I'm talking
about like the meaner Amina trench but
it's not sad tears it's like happy it's
a
you know like
yeah
anyway it's just oh geez and even now
even now I just don't take her emotions
seriously yet I expect her to take my
next seriously and it's just
it's I've got no energy you know if
you've got no energy to give for
yourself now how can you give it to
other people
you know like
I just wish I had oh it's kind of like
an online I'm more empathetic I am
because it's different it's there's a
giant Barrack here that can pause at any
time
but there it's just it's all this
package and we both got the same you
know
upset so it's not only my emotions it
has as well
but yeah it's just oh Jesus you know
like
now I understand it's just been at so
many it's so windy and it's annoying
it's ruining it's it's ruining the
smallest violin moment you know
it is as well I hope you can
but yeah it's just it's just it's just
awful
you know and it's kind of like
the experience was just oh my God
that just you know it was just
like I can confidently say that we know
other problems in my life nothing could
Trump that
you know and I'm glad for that I'm
grateful I wouldn't be the same person
without I really wouldn't be the same
person
yeah it's just
I've hear Fever song but
my nose is running I wonder if we could
jump down here
no I don't think we can anymore
but yeah
[Music]
I don't know it's just because I'm more
of aware of my fi so I'm likely it's
going to be like you know Show and Tell
like
here's the thing I've been found you
know I mean because I'm going to over
emphasize something I've discovered
recently I'm not going to talk about the
same record if I know it's something I'm
missing with information I didn't think
I'm missing on information
I don't I don't I really don't because I
just I look at another kind of sister
I'm just blind she's blind she really is
I'm like it's right in front of you
she'll freak out who it was she'll freak
out over things
but yeah just
I think that well
it's just just how oh God because I
would say things obviously it was when I
was like a kid so it's like I don't know
if I could use that
um
it's just
we're only 32 minutes maybe I can make
this actually palatable for someone
[Music]
it's just
like feeling other people's emotions and
feeling of the people's depths like
before I just add trash on them because
I can't see it it's my blinds but you
know
but it's just what they've
had questioned people's life experiences
I've questioned
we can go
there's like a little Bridge break
um oh it's really this way it's better
because of the wind but I don't know
it's just
all I know is that um the social Care
Systems [\h__\h]
really is it's just but you're on your
own you're on your own government's not
going to come to help you really like
this economy economic crash I know it's
nothing compared to what other people go
through like seriously no one has any
grasp of anyone's empathy because you
can't as a colony you can't just you
know give all your resources to other
people because you wouldn't exist as a
species anymore you know what you won't
be on top
but you know they would be donating
everything they had they're really truly
felt the empathy for other people
they'd be there
they would be giving every [\h__\h] last
penny to everyone
they could
but you know they're hooked on their
little door for me I'll get this nice
little thing that'll keep me going and
then you ostracize people who are
homeless
um for taking drugs when it's like
you're doing the same thing with all
your [\h__\h] list of items you bought
you know but
as I said we're born slave so that's our
trial of life and not saying it's a
negative thing we've got to be in our
ankle and we've got to be
gotta be something oh yeah you're gonna
be boring and have a free pass to do now
like you know you gotta do something
that's what we're all built for
it's just the point of which where do we
go from that well there's more people
you know like um
like where like I said you're gonna
travel around the universe like why do
you
where do we stop and where we were like
you know let's not
because once you externalize our
intelligence and sterilize you know
externalize our
um a Consciousness I suppose it gets to
the point where technology becomes
self-systematized
autonomous oh there's other people it's
kind of awkward
yeah
it's very awkward
another traps
the under inside
you think
I don't know
acquired
right um
yeah they're saying like
as I was saying
is that
that you know you get to that point
but it's like are we seriously doing the
right thing
are we
on the right course you know
it's squeezing this like like depression
obviously you gotta have depression
another thing I've noticed is like I
think we've do my fi if I do have fi
right at the bottom
is that it's essentially a
um like a tally chart and oh yeah better
than before that's like I don't know if
that's an Enneagram three thing I don't
know
but um it's like I thought it was stable
it was just I felt nothingness okay I
just I wasn't even in touch with what I
was feeling and it was just random
spikes down spikes up franticular
unpredictable and it would just be a
little balloon
oh they're actually ready oh we're going
to eat this summer yay but it would just
be this little blow up
of um
just anyone around anyone around because
it's like you popped my bubble I saw you
did that but essentially all it was well
Jesus it wasn't then I was just [\h__\h]
getting bigger and bigger and bigger
till I popped around them and I just
went you [\h__\h] blew me up [\h__\h] you and
you know and then assume that well I
cannot you know
with the emotion it's just Bloom up but
oh geez it's so easy to get rid of
a nice sad song You Know
and the FI attaches itself to this
subjective thing it can be anything
and it will just attach itself to it
um
and there you go and then you just
listen to it and just
because I essentially thought oh this
song is making me sad so I will skip it
um
and then obviously that's just like
ignoring the red alerts you know the
mind's like well this is going to be the
outlet not people it's gonna be this
song and then it's like nope this song
is awful let's skip it how dare it make
me feel so oh my storage is almost full
I will ignore
oh wait I'm on 37 minutes
I think it should be fine oh it's up to
40 minutes isn't it but yeah like um
the weather
but yeah um
I know I forgot what I was saying again
I feel like that's just my blast like
that's what I've
those are the things that I'm like
here's the best crops of my farm
but yeah I don't know
but yeah I feel like I'm very
entrepreneurial very optimistic
like get things done we can do it
together you know like pull through
oh [\h__\h] Jesus like
the hit Downs of life
especially when you've got no options
like I can't even paint the picture
because it's you know it's too grim
the pin and again like I say you know
it's kind of invalidating with my own
you know like oh this is awful it's like
that's not awful and it's kind of like
that it's like I'm weighing myself up
against the other FIS all the other
people
who's gonna kind of Judge I don't want
to be judges about passing as well
yeah
there you go
all I'm thinking now is like [\h__\h]
they're thinking about what I said
earlier
you know but
it's crazy I teared up a bit
my lips are so dry
it's awful
I should have drank more water
yeah and it's sunny
I don't really know what to say really I
hope the storage isn't run out deleted
so many apps so my screenshots I've got
like 10 000 screenshots it's crazy and
I'm like a bit of a hoarder there I'm
like oh I need to keep them all
but yeah I didn't
know really yeah
um oh but things that annoy me is that
oh we're getting behind
like getting behind or like delays
delays oh my God imagine going on a hike
you walk for 20 minutes or even one
minute and it's oh forgot something
gotta turn back I'm like oh
we could have been a mile ahead now and
now we're stuck
back at the start you know
that's very annoying
but yeah oh wait I forgot I remembered I
remembered I got a you know
just runny nose
really dry
but um yeah like I want to run a hotel
business something like this
like when I was younger God like I was
thinking I get cryogenically frozen
it's a little Channel chain to this one
because I remembered I get cryogenically
frozen
this was like when I was nine I was like
Googling it like oh I didn't want to die
and I felt really sad
but yeah I was and then I was thinking
um
but now all I'm thinking now is [\h__\h]
what's the land of the land of the law
gonna be then everyone's gonna have a
purpose you know will they use me as
some like Museum will I be in air for
like feeding me because about that
standard I will be a nip
I'm gonna Retreat around oh God
no that was there is that flower oh yeah
Wheats flower isn't it
I'm a bit slow today
um but yeah um but I really want to run
a hotel business or BNB an old self
ultimate the Japanese give me the idea
just have QR codes and then I can use it
as a summer home
but then all I imagine is that it's just
going to be so
not lonely but kind of pointless I often
shut myself down over the pointlessness
of things
of the well even when I do get that
still be in the middle or I just I'd hap
you know because the dopamine system
gets reset and it's like on to the next
thing Johnny you know you can't never be
happy can't never be satisfied
with anything
but then I'm also thinking well what's
the point of not trying what's the point
of not having those things you know
you're better than having it they're not
and that's like my main
you know everyone's gone through
depressions
you know everyone's gone through that
and it's just you lose all faith in
everything you believe in and it's just
recently it's just been like not
recently but it's like you know
a couple of years like
I lied it has been recently
I'm like no it's years ago it's fine
like you know but I've reconnected with
my old self like doing a lot of sleep
work of like this is my old passion this
is
this is who I was and wanted to be and
I'm like very much
getting back on track of that you know
yeah
doesn't know where I'm going
anyway
um