Okay, we've got 13 more minutes cuz I
deleted some videos and yeah, so that's
around 60 minutes, isn't
it? Anyways, um I was talking about my
friend and she would take more from me
than I would ever dream of asking from
them. Um so that was a big realization
of like, hey, what I'm offering versus
what I'm
receiving bipolar opposite, so why can't
I say no? And I'd say in a jerky way. I
started off saying like, "Oh, no." Like
in a silly American
accent.
Then sometimes I'd snap
though.
Yeah. Yeah. Cuz it was
just and I lost a few friendships from
that. that almost in itself it's like
either because it was too rapid of a a
change and like I was saying before
infancy dependency that I was causing on
them by doing things for them or it was
because they just didn't value me that
much and but also I can't I've learned
that I can't defend or rely on other
people to give me value also I don't
know if the hat's making it hard to see
imagine I do this like some [\h__\h]
weird American or something like what
the [\h__\h] no wait this is like
yo anyways but I was causing doing this
like um dependency thing, right? But
yeah, so I realized that my I can't
expect other people to give me value. I
can't expect them to do that. Um yeah,
I've learned this. Um so by
selfrespecting or self-putting in
annoyances or instead of hinting like,
"Hey, I'm annoyed by this other people
got to step in cuz if they cared, they
would by selfdoing that um people can
recognize that." Now I tried this out. I
did this
um and it just wasn't working. I was
like, wait, I was very pissed. I was
like, well, [\h__\h] them then. It didn't
work. I tried to do the fi I don't like
this. It's making me uncomfortable or
these jokes or these whatever. And it
wasn't working. So, I was like, well,
what the [\h__\h] the point? Like, this is
stupid. Um, I'll go back to slandering
them. But I learned that by consistency,
you can't build a character overnight.
You can't build selfrespect overnight.
So by me consistently doing that I
noticed a change that other people
started stepping in saying hey you know
you don't like that and it was working
and it does work it does work a lot more
um yeah and that so not only like I'm
getting help from others it's myself as
well to be able to say I don't like this
or I don't want to do this or you know
like things like that. Um so that was
that was very interesting very very
interesting to learn about that
um to trial that as
well. Okay.
Um the biggest challenge right now in
your life. The point here is to get talk
about you really care about drugs. No.
Um the thing I challenging thing Oh. Oh
yeah.
Um well I already know. I just don't
want to say it. Huh.
Um, well, I know three. It's like I have
to go to the dentist. There's like a
chip in my tooth thing, but I'm really
wor I don't want to go there. I don't
like that at all. It's the most
awkwardest thing. Um, having to go
there. No, I don't like that.
Um
um I have a check I need to cash
um as well that is from a savings
account from when I was 18 and everyone
in the UK got it. This is the socialism.
Everyone got money when they were born
during 2001 and
2011. Uh my sister missed out by one
year. So sad. Anyways, I haven't cashed
it still in 3 years. It's just sitting
there. I need to go into the bank to
cash that. I haven't done that.
Um, just awkward. It's awkward. I I
don't think I have the right paperwork
to go in and do that and it just makes
me feel embarrassed and
silly and stuff.
Yeah.
Um, but I know how to get it. It's just
it's a it's a long process. And yeah,
it's just I don't want to say why cuz it
just me saying why. Me saying the thing
that makes me uncomfortable would make
me uncomfortable. So why would I do
that, you
know? Um and all of a sudden thinking,
ooh, you think I'm an observer now cuz
thing issues. He doesn't have the right
paperwork. Oh, paperwork. Oh, is there
printer going to be next? Oh, you know,
well, tell me what you see. Hey.
Um, yeah. Um, right. So, tell us biggest
challenge there. the dentist check
thing. Um, oh, motivation. Motivation's
one as well. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Setting
up the device things as well and
managing them
all.
Um, confidence as well
probably.
Um, I'm sleep consumed. I've got all the
things I know.
My mind's blank. Biggest challenge.
Um, yeah,
it's I don't want to say don't want to
say um but it's
like issues related to SF things, you
know, fill in the gaps that that big
time. I feel like people won't accept me
for it big time.
Um, yeah. Very
sad. I feel like they
will. You know who you know who you are.
Um, oh l right. So, I've got nine 7
minutes left. 7 minutes and 60 seconds.
Right. Well, that's 8 minutes. That's 8
minutes. What am I
about? All right. So, what is what type
do you see yourself as? Why? Right. So,
I don't type myself. Didn't type myself.
Originally got ESFJ and then we did the
OPS flipping thing. Flippy.
Flippy. Uh, my sister typed me. She
typed me. Yes. It's been 4 years since
we got into ops. She has typed me double
masculine te ne play blast sleep consume
last type one which I added on the type
one thing but she did not disagree.
Other people in the group have also seen
this type in me. Um, some C ne
uh some C double fenamin some of that
but I think also going off audios and
this was when I was 19 as well but they
didn't know my age they thought I was 32
right um so if you're into visual typing
thing I don't think I'm double
phenomenon at 21 right you know just
saying especially when I was 19 as well
people thought I was like 32 and I was
like oh [\h__\h] and another thing I don't I
want to sit my real age cuz I felt like
I would be rejected from the group and I
wanted to learn more from this system
and stuff and it felt awkward. I felt
extremely awkward if I say my real age,
they'll feel like a [\h__\h] idiot cuz if
they've been speaking to a [\h__\h]
19year-old or an 18year-old and they've
been sharing [\h__\h] cuz we had like
in-depth conversations. I'm like, "Oh,
wait. They a lot of people thought I was
that age." I was like, "I never denied
it. I never said no." But I never said
yes at the same time. So,
um Yeah. Yeah. So, you know, so that was
very awkward as well. And just like when
I did say my age, it was like I felt so
cringe because I felt like I was
embarrassing then cuz they're like and a
lot of people didn't talk to me
afterwards cuz like Yeah, rightly so.
They're like, "Why would I speak to
someone that's half my [\h__\h] age?"
Yeah. Um Yep. And I don't like people
probably think I'm like, "Oh, a child."
And I know everyone says that. Everyone
that age says that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But it's just I feel like they wouldn't
respect what I had to say cuz they
thought I was older. Therefore, they'll
listen to what I've got to say a lot
more. And if they already listen to what
I say thinking that I was that age
anyways. If they think I'm younger and
they now devalue what I'm saying, which
a lot of people did because they don't
talk to me anymore, which yeah, that's
right. That's fine for them to do that.
Um I wouldn't if I was their age. I
think that's [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
weird. Lol. If anyone's watching, please
guys, I'm sorry if you are actually
watching this that they refuse to talk.
Also, we might have just drifted off and
I did go offline for a long time as
well, okay? So, I don't want to fully
throw anyone under the bus. And also,
I'm not even specifically mentioning
anyone. So, if you think it's you, then
you've got to deal with that yourself,
Sunny. I never mentioned anyone. So,
that's on you. Also, I feel like this is
angled a bit weird.
Um, yeah. And apparently, you can still
hear me. I listen back to the audio. It
worked just fine. I don't know why I go
like that with my eyes like Oh, also
channel change. This woman, she said
that the psychopath, so if you see
anyone that does this, be warned. And if
you do this, there is a 30% chance
you're a psychopath and going to kill
people. This woman, so this this
face, they do this face. Terrifying,
isn't it? The arousal of shock like
you're going over a roller coaster plus
joy. So like you know like that like
then
this and this is terrifying, isn't it?
Hi guys. Very scary warning flags in our
brain. Why do we have these warning
flags? evolutionary 30 to 40% of serial
killers, murderers, dictators, rapists
do they smile in the pictures
unconsciously. And I think it's linked
to their thinking of things. So they're
like, "Oh, we're family." And then
they're getting shocked, generally
aroused, terrified of their own thoughts
of what they were going to do. I feel
like they have these this these
thoughts. And now we all have random
thoughts of like, you know, kick that
child. No, I'm joking. But we do
actually have thoughts where it's like,
"Imagine if my phone dropped or imagine
if I threw my phone or if I dropped the
baby." Some people have these thoughts.
It's because it's the brain alerting you
of the danger and you going, "Oh my god,
why did I think of that?" Cuz it's
creating a little simulation of this is
real. This is a threat. This is a
possibility that's going to happen. So
yeah, again, these people, if you've
seen them, there's a 40% chance that
these people sacrifice if they do this
plus joy. So they're feeling joy and
they're shocked. And I think this is
what I've added on. the person that was
doing this didn't actually say this.
They're thinking of things and they're
like, "Oh yeah, imagine if I did that."
And they went, "Oh, imagine if I did do
that." Again, very scary. And I've seen
a few people that do that on pictures
and I'm like, "Whoa, red
flags." Again, I don't have enough time.
3 minutes. And I feel like because the
time is limiting me, I feel like I don't
have enough time to speak. Anyways, type
of thing I see myself as. And why? Well,
yeah. My sister typed me. She typed me.
I went off that long time. I was like,
"Oh, I'm an I'm a ESFP. I think I'm
really cool in NT, but no, I'm a
sensor." Was in a group chat for a long
time with many people. They were all
officially types. I thought we I all
thought we were sensors as well. All of
us. And I thought everyone was sensors
as well, to be honest. I was like, "Oh
yeah, we're all [\h__\h] sensors here.
Look at us. Every single [\h__\h] one.
INFP, ENTJ, INTP. [\h__\h] hell. Everyone
ENFP." And I was like, "Oh my god,
they're all N. What do you want about
they're all N? Where's her sensor?" So
that is a bit obviously that's not
directly me but everyone who in the
group who are N thought I was also N who
were officially typed as N by Dave Shan.
I know there's a lot of like you know
I'm visual. It's like yeah cuz you have
dog typed you you know I know people
probably appreciate Dave Shan. I get it.
I get it. I'm not official type
obviously. Hence why there's this
[\h__\h] video. Um yeah. Yeah. But um and
if you do the math you do the math. Oh
he channel changes a lot. Oh he's an
extrovert. Okay. OE. Oh, he's not giving
much detail. N. Oh, that makes him NE.
Oh, okay.
He's I don't know if I've shown DE, but
I've obviously shown play. I've
obviously shown blast. I'm got the
ability to share information whilst it's
not I'm leading with it, so therefore
play blast kind of thing. Um, a few
stories about self, a few I'm not as
intense as the sleep blasts I feel. So,
probably sorry, I'm I'm saying as if I'm
doing this moment. This is already
preset, but I'm saying like in the
moment with you, like doing it with you
is like if you can see what I'm seeing.
Also, I've got 2 minutes to wrap this
up. So, I'm not that intense as a sleep
blast. I've got memories from when I was
a kid. I've got I can go a bit d deep
diap into the emotions. I can go a bit
deep into the emotions and [\h__\h] A
little bit goofy, but not that much. I
know that's anecdotal. Um, so yeah. So,
I think that Yeah, obviously that's
high. Extrovert, high player, high
blast. There you go. Doesn't shut up.
hasn't shut up for this long time. So,
there's consume last. Um, maybe maybe I
think you'll see me as a double decider.
However, I did talk about the politics
thing that was a bit on the nay side of
like that's a bit missing the vibe and
the but then me saying that might make
you think I'm a double decider because I
can see that. But people point this out,
right? I've done these videos before.
I've watched them back. Cringe as [\h__\h]
But I've realized that with other people
who are really bad in friendships groups
and even online groups as well,
individuals that are like doing [\h__\h]
that's really cunnish. I thought I was
the worst guy. Meanwhile, I see them and
I'm like, "Oh, that's what people are
looking at." They're looking at them.
I'm like, "Oh, okay. I I feel much more
confident and settled in myself to be
like, "Yeah, I think I'm a pretty chill
guy, pretty genuine guy, you know, and
that and I'm okay with saying that now
without, you know, being narcissistic
for having selfworth and all these other
things." So yeah. So yeah, type I see
myself as is the type my sister's given
me. And yeah, there you go. You're
probably going to say ENFP jumper
probably cuz there's a bit of like um 7
seconds left. There was a bit of
closeness with the FI. I didn't want to
share full. I wasn't as open with the FE
of like emotions and stuff. And it