okay okay so this one's going to be 32
minutes long it's the same um phone I
just deleted some apps um yep so that
makes the video to 54 minutes which is
in the time frame okay so what is wrong
with the government politics these days
okay well before you would have been
like oh immigration and things like that
um you know based off the right so I
know the if you're SF and you're
watching this yeah you're missing the NT
so if you have a B for it of the
population's not making as many kids
right and it's shrinking by 25% with
each generation and you have immigration
of 2 million coming in one year every
year it's around 800,000 in the UK very
high amount or around 300,000 something
around that actually matches the
abortion rate which is pretty
interesting y you're not going to like
that yeah don't care if you're triggered
then you're just rejecting the part of
society that you don't want to listen to
we're all mines hive mind [\h__\h] so if
this is a part that you're triggered by
that's your neurons that you going have
developed so there you go and it so yet
so it would have been immigration it
would have been things like that fire
right politics and stuff cuz it's like
yeah if you got loads of people coming
in what do you expect these people are
elit by the way these people aren't poor
especially refugees other thing they
came with nothing mostly men secondly if
I right most people in the UK can afford
to just uproot themselves and move 5,000
Mi across the world in the UK our wages
are higher our currency stronger and we
have better transport links than in
[\h__\h] Syria all anywhere yet somehow
these people come thousands of miles
they probably sell their kids along the
way and I'm not kidding that is a true
fact not all of them obviously but still
yet somehow they make it over somehow
they got the money and they have their
enough food and they have money to play
these Smugglers 10,000 each and the news
headlines who were like 10,000 it's like
they're scamming them it's like well why
do they have 10 grand to spend 10,000 in
UK money in their money is worth so much
more that's extreme amount and
especially during a war that's been
lasting 30 years how do they have the
econ economy how do they even have the
business or anything to make money in
there unless it was human trafficking
drug smuggling selling children or
something like that these people are
criminals we don't know who they are
they burn the passport yeah so that's my
view that's my yeah missing the NF
whatever that is but it's true these are
truths I know they're not only the thing
but it's something that just doesn't
make [\h__\h] sense if you worry about
house prices doubling every year well
you've got Mass open borders for the
elites to buy houses when our population
shrinking the native population which
includes people of all colors I'm not
just talking about English people but
you know incluses everyone their
population is decreasing yet our
population is increasing the children
aren't being born yet more people are
coming over how are prices going up it's
not immigrant obviously it is obviously
it is no it's the mean people the top
it's like no they wouldn't do that cuz
obviously they won't be able to sell as
much you know you know nah [\h__\h]
anyways that's my little triggering
thing and we did right in the UK I
stopped a bus I stopped a
bus I didn't have an English flag I had
an Australian flag really weird but
someone kind of went hey it's close
enough I was like yeah
yeah oh my
God crazy yeah but also I have swings
where I'm like yeah true we should be
more compassionate and stuff but also
the end of the day be much more it's is
just most people if they have the
ability to uproot themselves and travel
thousands of miles they aren't doing it
on foot and if they are where they're
getting the food from where they're
getting the money from you know so it's
just a few questions that that Mak sense
though right so and a lot of the videos
online are usually like um like milit
military they they War um I think our
government's paying them cuz they're
General officials so they come over for
Asylum yet because they've got they're
[\h__\h] on their own people they're
[\h__\h] on their own government cuz
things are going to [\h__\h] that's what I
think is happening um yeah but the
people that coming over the immigrants
they're not poor people they're not poor
people you have to have earn a threshold
you have to have like at least 30k if
you want to enter the UK so yeah these
aren't like the poor these are the ultra
Rich so if you SF types don't like the
rich yeah that's the people coming but
you filter it through oh no they're of
color in the UK the UK judge system they
implemented based off race so you'll get
sentenced if you're a minority gay or a
woman your sentencing will be reduced
based off your
ethnicity you know I understand that
they're trying to level things up
because of the UN playing field they
they're looking at surface value of oh
These people aren't equal yeah cuz they
only just came 50 years ago if you spec
generationally in two generations for
people to go from the bottom with
nothing just arriving in a new place to
get to the top the fact that we have a
lot of people in government who are
minorities we actually have
disproportionately we have more people
with minorities than white English
people in the government despite
immigration only just starting around 50
years ago around 1945 it started every
year it was around 4 to 5,000 people
very small numbers in the 70s it kicked
off whereas in tens of thousands now it
was 1.3 million last year the year
before that's 600,000 so we're wrapping
things up um yeah so that's why we have
that is that is why they're wrong
because obviously if you think there's
some institutionalized thing
how can it just it's because in 50 years
if you're expecting people to go from
zero to the top when other people have
been here for thousands of years what do
you expect also they actually are rising
to the top but to try to speed up
integration or speed up um you know
equality is going to cause friction and
is going to cause rights just like
inflation with the economy if the NT is
try and speed up the economy they try to
speed up the St oh no inflation oh [\h__\h]
what have you done done then you've got
the and people are poor then you got the
NFS trying to speed up the SF and then
you go riots you got more prees you got
lots of conflicts and everything like
that so yeah also bit weird cuz my
neighbors are
minorities so that's not the best but
you know so I don't want them thinking
I'm like a racist or anything and all
like you know right you ready probably
comes to a shock is a sodomite so [\h__\h]
you I'm not as bad as you think I
am also I don't know if you can hear me
or not because I don't actually have if
I till it slightly the mic is underneath
and it's PR it's fced up so if it's like
pressed usually I cover it with my
finger and people can't hear me I'm like
[\h__\h] anyways
um yeah so tell
us yeah so oh sorry I didn't even get to
that was my old I say old but I'm
clearly still annoyed by it um yeah so
that was my little
I say a little but I'm a bit clearly a
bit annoyed by
it um so the government now it's um
temperaments it's much with Ops I've
realized that yeah I'm I'm clustering on
this side with more thinker [\h__\h]
traditionally or whatever you want to
call it if it's that if it's thinker
it's feeler if it's right or left it's
it's obviously right I'm missing the F
cuz if all I can list is Right issues
where the left are going wrong and I'm
just seeing look they've got this wrong
this wrong this wrong and I'm got it
right right here right right good good
good I'm biased cuz if they can't say
where they're doing wrong but they know
where they're going if they can is
everyone points out the finger right so
if they can call out others but can't
call out themselves they're extremists
and so am I so yeah it's just about
accepting what I can't see fully and
that so um and this also ties into
another thing of um and I know I'm
Channel changing but hey why not I want
to and this is what I want to say with
groups of people minorities so give
people more likes to be pedophilic um
sexualization of kids degeneracy shallow
relationships sex fests public displays
of nudity um AIDS is a fetish and they
have it on the dating apps they have it
on the hookup apps there's a category
called um neg for PA negative for
positive and BB which is a form of
unprotected sex they have um uh Chasers
which means someone wants to chase a
disease and actually be infected by it
but catches poisonous Lord things like
this it's normalized it is across the
culture and this is why the Bible and no
no means religious but this thing passes
through time why they were so against
men or men cuz men have higher sex drive
they're always up for it it just keeps
going on high the dopamine system resets
they want something more and more and
that's that's where we get this extreme
event where you got people in lever Kink
gear you got people in animal costumes
beastality it's it's and that's there
you know on the apps they have that they
have beastality and I report and they
say sorry this is not against the rule
he's like I love [\h__\h] dogs and I said
it's in the buyer and I got an email
back saying sorry this doesn't go
against our
policy right and guess what the company
only hires gar people oh so it's an
inside loop reason why people don't self
call this out so not only do the others
so you got gear people and you got
straight people they are calling them
out everyone points the finger at the
small group of people don't selfo the
finger rarely some people do and I do
that and guess what the reason why many
other people don't is cuz not only am I
getting ostracized by straight people
naturally so I understand why but still
not to the extent I agree with I can
understand that like you know homophobia
things like that does exist so that's
why people don't want to call themselves
out cuz at risk of being rejected even
more if they than they already are but
gar people reject me myself when I was
18 they were coming after me like
Hornets cuz it was a trans uh um trans
male I have an issue with him but there
was they were putting a Pur up saying
that trans women have zero biological
advantage to biological women simply
untrue I'm not saying they shouldn't be
as valid but some types are missing the
F and the T together and can't see that
so they're like it's only all acceptance
and if you say any T that makes no sense
you're saying they're not as valid Leo
Thomas 6'4 is not as valid [\h__\h]
they're missing [\h__\h] just as I'm missing
things as well um so yeah so like um
that's that so like
um they came after me messaged loads of
people I was blocked by many people in
the gay community and [\h__\h] like that and
yeah so that happens a lot happens with
Islam and pedophilia and you know they
the thing is this is how this happens is
like um it's a cognitive distance thing
it's in every single group white people
with racism it's hard for us to accept
that men and violence against women
because as a male if you accept that
this exists you now have to be
responsible for that you have to call it
out when you see you have to defend them
cuz you just told us it exists so if you
acknowledge it exists then you have to
do it you have to engage within this
thing so you can't just act like this
doesn't exist anymore so it's easy to go
nah it's not but and I think it's a
traditional standpoint of view to
protect women that's a that is not a
work thing that is traditionalism but
somehow this is seen as work now that's
a bit weird that's that's gone a bit too
far like no qualities where men can
punch them back I'm like shut the [\h__\h]
up that's stupid it's [\h__\h] um any so
like the reason why we have these things
is cuz we don't want to be we're wor
another thing is we're worried what
we'll do to they'll do to us what we did
to them there's an imbalance of power
we're worried once the power is given
they'll take more and more and more
because of Revenge of many different
things so it's understandable and but
yes so many different groups minorities
it suffen since 99% of London stabbings
are by black men in so that's a huge
statistic I have to be quiet because my
neighbors are you know anyways
that is a huge disproportionate amount
now of course that is going to be for me
to call this out is worrying some of
these people but once a black person
does it's kind of like a oh what do we
do with the left like it's a little
brainfall cuz it's but it's it's exactly
what they wanted it to do if the left
knew what their purpose was it was to
integrate people to feel comfortable
enough in all aspects of life where they
can be and safe in different groups of
people where everyone accepts them if
gay people are on the right left and me
like black men are on the right talking
about these issues women are no longer
feminists but now traditionalists or
whatever they've done their job they've
done their job cuz now they are actually
comfortable to be on the enemy side if
the people you're trying to protect have
gone to the enemy side of the right then
they're no longer a threat to the
society they're no longer needed to be
lifted up and often times they're
actually thrown under the bus it's hard
for me to track this it's probably an Fe
thing so like with Islam it's you know
they're homophobic as [\h__\h] right no lie
about that and when people say that
they're against Islam having influence
in the society they're saying that's
islamophobic because they'll say it
right so we're against homophobia and
sexism very moral things but it's
islamophobic if it's islamophobic that
means Islam sexist and homophobic why
would you want that but it's a bit of it
doesn't make sense to me and this is
what's been happening in the UK um their
role is just to anyone who's hated for
any [\h__\h] reason just to protect them
understandably cuz I think it's some
evolutionary trp from The Witch Hunt
you know when we have these women just
being bent for no [\h__\h] reason it's
like oh [\h__\h] my nles look they can
see it's like the balcony doors
open um and I can like we can see to the
next house and he's kind of in his
window so it's a bit weird thought those
bads are so lot as well it's a bit
distracting
um yeah it's been really warm today so I
got the doors open so it's nice cuz
it's it was around 14 de today but when
the Sun's shining it's just hot hot hot
hot so I need the cooler air and now you
get down to minus one which is in
Fahrenheit if you're an American I know
one person is it is around 32 31 F and
then the daytime's around 50 60 F so
for me that's very warm very very warm
especially when you're used to the
winter time and it's below zero no
sunlight you know and I've been I've
been tanning as well a bit probably bit
sunburn if you can see yeah so anyways
oh okay well I've actually not even
spoken about the real issue that I think
now okay so the problem politics is
types there's not enough types we're
screwing back and forth humans are only
so smart if you're buring People based
off popularity and not skill set all
these things it's just a constant
Balancing Act Right um and everyone's
trying to pull in that little snippet of
information of what we should do I think
technology should start having a girl
try it give it a girl see what happens
yeah it's just people and type that's
the biggest issue now constantly missing
each of
us deficit and it's just a stupid thing
especially when you can see now with VPS
you're like oh they're stuck on that oh
they're stuck on this it's like are you
[\h__\h] kidding me your entire life has
been wasted on this little snippet of
information move on get on with things
do what you want to do instead of just
fixating and I know I'm probably also
fixating just like the thing I just did
before that was a bit you know I
couldn't even even though that's what I
used to think I'm still stuck on it I'm
still getting into it like right I got
to whisper oh the it's bad it's this and
that you know so yeah still it still
affects me my brain's still tied to this
so yeah also I have 15 minutes left I'm
glad it's just I don't want to delete
any more apps this is a good phone to
use the other PHS I use for the data
things and the camera it's like a crappy
phone cuz I don't need it to be my phone
to use it's getting a bit dark I don't
know if you can see me fully um I can
put up the BR
though that did
anything it's just going back and forth
um yeah so um it's getting dark now and
it's actually 7:33 the clocks went
forward in summer it is dark at 11:00
p.m. and light at 3:00 a.m. it's
beautiful time we're extremely not off
for it as high as Alaska it's beautiful
time of year I love it it goes so fast
though it goes so fast so around March
September the Equinox the whole world
has the same amount it's just 12h hour
days but um cuz it tilts in the sun it
literally I'm up here so even when this
Earth moves around it's still shining
there and it's just constant daylight
constant practically in Scotland you can
read a book at night it's very nice and
then then in Norway obviously you've
seen it midnight sun I know you know
about that [\h__\h] yeah um love it love it
so [\h__\h] much absolutely incredible
love it great time of year can be out
you're awake all the time 3:00 a.m. 4:00
a.m. you can be outside you'll have no
you will have no idea hardly anyone
outside it just feels like the wild is
for your own it's just beautiful sunsets
last around 3 hours um it's like a
beautiful pink and it's just a very
Golden Sun it's just you know really
good [\h__\h] I might have to put a light on
soon cuz it's getting dark cuz
apparently to see my face and I'm
probably not looking at the camera as
much as I think I am which right not
might not be the best I was going to
wear a hat as well cuz um my hair but um
I think I look I look better with the
hat on right you know I look more
human so might keep this on but also I'm
going to put a light on so be one minute
and I'm worried you'll see something you
don't want to see cuz I'm not actually
dressed so imagine I flashed
myself so I'm going to go this
way I me one
minute oh my
God oh my God
okay that's bad nothing flashed um yeah
sir I don't know I think I think it's
better with the hat on um I prefer it
this way I don't look as bald or
cancerous right um tell us a story about
the worst and best I feel like I don't
have enough time it's really annoying um
cuz the time is scking down I'm like oh
only 10 14 minutes like oh no I want
more time um I could always use the
other Fone though so tell us a story
about the best or worst time in your
life um oh sorry the politics thing yeah
is just people type missing each other's
point of view of that [\h__\h] just an
endless this and that and this and that
previous party does things socialism
then the next party undoes the socialism
cuz the socialism cause problems you
look at on the Spectrum you have North
Korea almost 100% socialist America the
most capitalist Society but do you
wanted to get the true socialist society
African Hunter gavas that's true
socialism to the most extreme extent
then you have English medieval peasants
where there's one guy the lord of the
land that everyone works too that's the
Spectrum and the UK is a bit too
socialist very socialist um and it's
stagnating growth and the people who are
like oh we need to take the rich thing
and tax the rich it's myopic it's too
shortsighted you're going to run out of
other people's money to spend and it
slows things down if you would rather
have Elon must building a rocket that
gets us to Mars or paying his workers a
bit more oh monster andage drinks
takeaways wow if our resources are so
finite and limited I think I use that
word wrong five night SLS they're so
limited why do you want people spending
more on [\h__\h] Monster eny drinks and
takeaways people don't spend money
wisely the reason elon's at the top or
whoever you might go in his history I
don't know but whoever gets to the top
there is nothing there's no one out
there it's just capitalism it's EP ISM
it's all every type does what they want
to do and if they if you can convince
someone to provide a service or do a job
for them and they'll part with their
money humans choose to part with their
money no one's forcing people to work
for youone they're doing it on his their
own choice he's giving them a price and
they're willing to pay for it it's
ridiculous everything he's selling as
well his internet services Rockets all
Teslas people are buying them you cannot
force or mandate people not to spend
their money that is communism that is by
force it's a for town you if you don't
like that people are spending their
money in other ways from people you
don't like first of all you're poor as
[\h__\h] cuz you can't afford that [\h__\h]
anyways secondly shut the [\h__\h] up you're
just a stupid idiot you know you
seriously they're silly they're very
very silly because it's just again if
these people got more money less money
going to Mars more money on the Little
Rock and more money going on takeaways
and stupid things that are insignificant
long term no and obviously everyone
advances now I don't think it fully
advances cuz obviously Eastern
Europe didn't so for instance capitalism
seems to actually operate where has to
have another country that was Communist
turn into capitalist to try and undo
that so I'm like um are we actually
Advanced as we think we are I'm like is
it true is it true could this be a lie
who
knows all right so the um again don't
feel like I've got enough
time um tell us a story about the best
or worst time of your life oh and or
okay I got two um okay well I could talk
about the worst it was like it's like
this film it's called Lifeline I think
it's this Australian film um she's
trapped in a prison for a year and she's
away this is started during Co actually
um yeah of just isolation from so like
my M had left I was alone me my sister I
was 15 and yeah um my sister was 19 just
turned to 18 sorry she was 18 yeah we
were both literally
teenagers no support no nothing um yeah
horrendous horrendous I'm very glad I
went through that though if I didn't go
through that I wouldn't be the person I
am today I
have a lot of things I need to process
still on that um but this is 6 years ago
again I do worry I used to worry I used
to worry oh the thing that happened to
me is traumatic it's a sad situation
that obviously has impacted me in some
way therefore my brain is Tainted it's
ill therefore no one would want me
because why would they want a damaged
product but now I'm realizing the more I
listen to like NF types of people and
all this culture where it's acceptable
and the more I ask people for validation
to affirm me it's that it makes people
more resilient it makes
people tougher it makes it's it's like I
survive that and I know that sounds a
bit weird though but I did I did like
you know
i' it's kind of like a premature baby in
a way like you know um but I did it was
horrendous very bad very very bad time
incredibly tough
yeah no not good at all um yeah
completely gone though we we climbed out
of that [\h__\h] on our own seriously on our
own um and I think that's the best thing
though like stress wise I would have
many stresses in the future because of
it cuz like if you have a fresh hold and
you're being down here anything that's
like societal stresses that's here yeah
if I go down here I'm still higher than
the where I was before so yeah no issues
there
um yeah very painful very frustrating
extremely angry extremely frustrating
time um I would never wish this on
anyone I'd never want to go through it
again I would not be able to go through
that again no awful abs absolutely awful
time um
yeah um I don't really remember much of
it um because it was just the same same
thing every single day exact same
thing
um same worries
same
helplessness I kind of cut myself off
from the worlds but also it's curved as
well
yeah Social Services are very bad very
bad at the job very failed big time um
us they really
did
um also we we're very isolationist as
well so we didn't really fully accept
Health but I'm sorry but if someone's 15
and someone's 18 and like their sister's
looking after their
brother
um yeah you should step
in
anyways I'm yeah so that situation
obviously had to climb out of that build
myself a find an income source which
luckily I did so did my sister um
budgeting budgeting is Big Time
budgeting learning how to budget best
learning how to you know clean the pots
properly um Hy like you know learning
how to take care of yourself properly
you know when you've got a parent doing
all of this at age 15 and then and it
started at 14 so it was like you know
just such a SW sudden
switch
um it's it's you got to learn these
things you know you've got to learn how
to keep things clean and all that which
we weren't doing and things piled up big
time and what we cleaned it we we we
managed to
undo the things that we weren't doing
and now we're everything's yeah with'
Lear systems and and finding the energy
to do that um obviously years back now
it was yesterday we finally did it we
managed to do it six
years but yeah that was a very um
hopelessness no will to live
nothing for around 4 years didn't want
to no reason to and my the thing that
made me think of keep on going is like
why not let's just see you know cuz like
short there a lot of time like it was
just the point of like Okay then if it
is better then great if it's not well
you know what so yeah no it's not nice
um no not nice at all
um best point of my life was when I was
younger very cry very
very ner thoughts of the world
um yeah
no thoughts of the world at all Carefree
very fun didn't feel judged all I'm tall
like I'm pretty
tall 6' five um so that's the top
99.99% of men so I do stand out so
obviously that adds to the people are
looking at me I don't like being outside
but as a kid obviously I'm small
everyone's taller I'm Carefree by nature
and stuff but yeah
um best moment of my life though
um it's not now no but it's improving
every month I feel better I feel I can
see things more clearly I'm advancing on
things projects I want to work on you
know um so like
Fitness um Health diet as well as well
um saving money making money things like
there's plans as well and confidence is
Big that I'm working on as well used to
not be able to go in the store alone I'd
have to ask friends like oh you free oh
can you come in the shop with me oh my
God oh my sister as
well yeah big time and it's still
awkward as [\h__\h] I don't like it I don't
like it I feel like people are watching
what I buy I feel like the and fr go as
[\h__\h] I buy cheaper products I don't
want to spend three times for the same
thing right so
also use an app um I don't know if I
should tell you cuz then you'll use it
and I don't want you using it cuz I want
all the goodies basically it's like a
concept where it's like okay so you have
store sells things and things are so
McDonald's Starbucks any type of store
you know supermarkets um where they
anything that doesn't sell that's going
off within the next day or the best
before so not even like used by D best
before is when things don't taste as
good the quality aspect and then you
have used by which is when bacteria
going start growing soon you want to eat
it now right so consumption safety rate
and it's it's all the best before it and
yeah so anything that doesn't sell it's
marked down by around 80% so my food
costs are extremely low hence why I can
get away with like not having a job and
just using data WS from these fs and
stuff and I managed to save we don't
have any DS we don't have any and I say
we cuz um like yeah like I Tred to we
kind of matage things as well
yeah and also cuz like yeah we live in
the same property like rents rent for
both of us you know
half and stuff um but yeah we was in
depth though by overdraft cuz that's
what we was using after well it was my
sister's overdraft it was 2000 it got to
that's all paid off um again this
reversal this like got to a point where
we sank so
low that for some reason mostly summer I
tie to summer when it's summer it's nice
it's warm
so but it was hell it was actual hell um
but we managed to PIR everything off um
but again like that's just the lack of
support from the things
like
yeah but we paid it off fully a year ago
which is great um yeah now we're saving
so that's great that's really good
um I often like to look at the charts
where it's like your age and how much
you should have saved and I'm like ooh
I'm above the average love that love
that so much definitely feel like I have
to be probably we I'm wearing a hat as
well cuz like oh my hair is not like
Grand there's a funny reason why I did
this I will not be saying though but
someone watching
[Music]
knows you
know oh god um yeah obviously a lot of
times i' feel like I oh I've got 1
minute left great okay I I'll recall
this on my other phone as well cuz I do
want to keep speaking but a lot of times
I thought that people think I'm toxic
it's i' I've known NPS for 4 years and
mbti for another year so um my and this
ties into the next question of what type
I am but like my sisters typed me people
around me have typed me and they all say
the same thing and they've been pointing
things out about me so I've spent four
or five years working on this [\h__\h]
seeking reassurance for it's like is it
okay if I say that and watching other
people and realizing and and comparing
to hey when people ask me for things
like if they're ask like a cigarette or
something I'm like oh yeah sh take take
four take four and I'd give them four
and then I would be like there were so
confident asking I would never ask that
and I'd be pissed like why did I even do
that I would give a homeless person food
and I'm like I wanted to eat that why
did I do that I'm thirsty so just kind
of do it in the moment and then be like
why did I do that um and I've realized
like it's like um oh so back to the
thing if they can ask then I can say no
if they're so confident and cocky for
them to ask something for me then I can
say no to them and if they're
embarrassed then they're embarrassed I'd
be so embarrassed to even ask so why
can't I say no so it was these questions
that I was like and my friend Lauren
she's been helping me with this a lot
like I stamped her foot in the shop
though cuz I wanted to buy a vape and
they said the wrong flavor I wanted Cola
she said watermelon and then my friend
was like you know speaking cuz she knows
I'm very passive like oh no it's fine
and she was like oh no it's not that one
I won't shut the [\h__\h] up I stamped on
her foot The woman there saw she was
like what the [\h__\h] did he just do and
I'm like it's fine oh man it was more
awkward and this is another thing it's
like I've got 30 seconds but I am
respecting my fi by doing that even
though you might think oh that's de I
feel like that's fi cuz it makes me
uncomfortable to sit there and [\h__\h]
say Oh no you're wrong I want this one
even it's a product I'm paying for I
have to speak faster cuz I got 6 seconds
in fact I'm going to do another video