well I cut off sorry part two
I think I can upload it like this
but yeah I think that's just been you
know getting back on track of like who I
was and how determined I was
but it's just when you hit a low it's
just you lose everything there's no
point to anything and I I was always
theorizing like you know like usually
people shut themselves off you know
become a recluse
but I was thinking the reason is that is
like the brain's kind of ramping itself
up it's preparing itself for after you
know it's you know I mean like it's it's
fixing whatever problems in front of it
and you know this like the amygdala
expands and the hippocampus shrinks you
know
because it's just getting ramped up for
the stress that could be coming
to get you prepared you know you can't
be exchanging information with people or
wasting time on other things and when
there's things that are coming or things
that are currently happening
so you know and but I think once after
it
people just become Unstoppable
and this story is it's just it's just
lovely it's just
oh there's a dried up Slug and a
butterfly but you know these stories are
just lovely
what they've done
um but yeah and the things they've
overcome
um but yeah
I've only got 18 minutes left I don't
know what to talk about
but yeah I think that
I don't know really it's just so Random
like I'm not even seeing anything I
don't think I'm saying things I feel as
if I'm just like
it is just uh
ping has one point and
you know but um
yeah just on a scroll in the mud
it's all dry
oh it's gonna be really hot today as
well 27 degrees which is if we do the
math we do the fahrenheit so you've got
a plus 32 I don't know why you still use
your colonizers
um measurement as well we've got 32 plus
27 which equals 59 imagine it's wrong
it's like Jesus and then you've got a
div wait 59 then you've got a I think
I'm gonna divide it by nine which would
be um I don't think I've got ti so bear
with me
so 59 wait is it 50 yeah 59 divided by 9
which would equal
five six
point oh
six point where where
seven
no yeah I think 6.7 Times by five which
would be
oh God fatty
itching my bum 33.3 degrees that's way
off it's not it's not freezing here
right now
anyway there you go you're welcome wait
wasn't I supposed to times it
I don't know see this is I feel like
this is the sensory
like would math be oh my God there's a
deer lovely
some beautiful things to show you
I feel like I'm gonna delete well I
can't can I oh it's a horse I am in a
horse field
lovely
I don't want to get kicked by them
they're super freaked out
but yeah like um
wait like the biggest problem with
people
is um I'm literally just itching my ass
I've got really bad diarrhea this
morning it was awful
it's like a cannon it was like what
I don't know if that's a deer or a horse
yeah lovely Fields oh pretty pretty
lovely Greenery but from the boxes
that's a deer oh [\h__\h] oh my God there's
loads
well that's nice
oh the landing on me oh this is so weird
you see it
I don't think you can see it there's
lots of butterflies flying around it's
really nice
but yeah um
I don't have another questions so I
don't even know what to like I've not
got no prompts what to talk about
but yeah I think other people it's the
same guy
but yeah
um as before
I don't know if I'm peacocking on
tuition
because I used to explain my analogies
and then I felt really dumb
so I started not explaining them
now people don't understand
can't win I think this is a field of
lavender
something like that
who knows oh I know where this leads
it's fine
Road
but yeah um well we have 10 minutes left
um I hope I give enough substance of
something
um
but then if it's up my authentic self
in the am I really just incorrectly
sharing
myself in that I'm sharing
um I'm sharing things that I've recently
discovered I know about
you know
um but yeah I do want to set up a
business
and very much Channel changing
throughout this like it's ridiculous
but I do want to set up a business
around the world in every little
location
it's nice it's like you can just live
there
like a holiday home then run it out when
you're not there you know sounds great
in theory
but it's just
you know like doing it doing it oh my
God you can have unlimited energy you
can do it it's but the brain just it's
kind of like you just randomly like a
little checklist like you are going to
be selected to make it there and do your
dreams the other people they're just
going to be built for complaining
and they'll complain and complain and
complain and they'll never get there
you know you'll be like you'll say stop
complaining to them and they'll get
pissed and I'm like ah you see that's
your little coping mechanism to shut you
off from your goals and your dreams
yeah because you can't have everyone
getting there you know can have everyone
there has to be some hierarchy
um
yeah
I don't know really I'm not I'm not
gonna record it again I cannot talk for
an hour again my storage is already full
and this is literally just going out 5
A.M
doing it so I think this is the most
I think that's the best that you can get
of just randomness of you know
yeah
God I I was ugh that's cringe
but it's authentic isn't it what I said
earlier
but yeah I just think that
I don't know how much Ops has influenced
my answers and understanding
because my biggest deficit
um was immersions at the time that's
what I thought I was an ENFJ lip result
you know ESTJ
um so I thought oh well I've got to find
my FIS that's the most compatible
I just got blocked after blocks after
what I was just saying like things like
oh I hope your dog dies in your arms or
I hope she drowns and you can't see her
again and she's like it's funny it's
funny I don't care if you think it's
different like that's disgusting it's
like good good okay you're a moral
person you're not you know you're you're
in the system you're not like a you know
your own mind
um
I feel like John Rivers I relate to her
a lot
John Rivers is I didn't even know she
died
I was watching her for years I didn't
even know I got I've I found her out
after she died but I didn't know she was
dead that's what I got into her I was
watching her for years and then I
literally found out two weeks ago she
died and I was like what 2014 as well
Jesus
yeah
yeah but um there you go I think that's
that's my typing video
um but as I say you know if I'm
I've recognized if I've really pulled
those two pieces together it will look
like oh there's the FI and the T very
close it's like ah you've got it oh I've
been stung by Nettles
[\h__\h]
ah
I don't know
hey what a route
but um
but yeah
so it will look a different way I don't
know am I talking about things am I
talking about people
um
but that's the thing if I'm talking
about myself and being asked to talk to
myself I'm gonna get my sleep work
you know because I recognize what sleep
is
um I don't know
yeah well there you go micro analyze me
I don't I feel like I want to say
something
and I can't remember what it was that I
wanted to see
um oh there's a horse up close you can
see huh
[Music]
hello oh
don't eat me
oh
well that's nice isn't it
a nice ending see all I think is it's
gonna I don't think it's gonna boot me
in my face
anyway
I usually come with apples but my God's
plan today I should have brought them as
well
yeah
oh that'd be great with it like
completing a horse at the end of the
video
but yeah um
yeah
but yeah I think it's just
people I know
yeah it's that it's just
yeah I think oh
these I think these are opium things I
don't know
I can't remember
and
psychopath there was a pigeon
yeah I think
I don't know
this is it you're welcome everybody
um oh God its neck is so long
oh
I can't remember what I was gonna say
and I'm going to be very disappointed
because I think that's all the sleep
I've got you know
or things I've got
I don't think I spoke about my interests
as much
um
I was definitely [\h__\h] Channel
changing the [\h__\h] out of everything
yeah my mind blanketed blank try and go
back
and the camera's been down here it's not
even up here look oh you can see the
curvature of the Earth
it's not flat
but yeah I think that's it I don't think
I've got anything else on my mind
probably will do later
and that'll be very
ugh I'm just thinking about what I spoke
about earlier
I think there's an accident I don't know
it's nothing oh it's nothing like oh I
don't know what you're thinking you're
probably making assumptions about it if
you are done because
it's again I said you're it's
invalidating
it's not the real thing
oh there's another butterfly
enjoy it yeah I think that's it I don't
really have anything else to say I don't
think
so um yeah
yeah there you go I don't know I feel
like there's something there's obviously
something because I've gone on a walk to
do this
you know and just I don't know maybe I
should have done it sat down but then I
was also kind of like I don't want other
people hearing it
and then I'm also thinking my neighbors
can hear me
um
and I thought it'd be most honest or at
least factual or correct if I'm walking
whilst talking
um because the mind can't you know I
mean it's like juggling with things
you've got not necessarily gonna be
um you're not going to necessarily be
um
forgot the wet like this right now you
know you can't pretend to be something
or not whilst also trying to walk
through a [\h__\h] field passing people
there's so many things changing your
mind that
it's like doing an accent you know
someone's you're talking to someone and
you're doing all these other tasks and
you're not going to be able to continue
doing the accent