right so this is the typing video um
I've used a chair and a salt shaker to
prop my phone up I've got many FS you'll
hear about that later for the
questions and yeah I'm going to answer
the
questions I just need to get them up and
this is very [\h__\h] awkward I don't
like this at
all okay so question one is um what is
your average day and week like oh
this kind of ties in with the question
um one minute see this is so awkward man
I don't like this at
all it's it's tiing with the first one
isn't it I thought they was like oh what
do you do and I'm like oh that's
question three okay so question
one also I have a cough which isn't
helping what is my average day and week
like practically non-existent it's
mostly seasonal so my whever I get up in
the morning is based off the Sunrise so
I live in the UK very far north around
near
Alaska sorry it's just I'm watching
myself on the
video so it's a bit weird um and again
the cough so in Winter we have 6 and 1/
half hour days so I don't do much I
don't do much it's cold it's dark unless
it's like freezing fog then I'll go on a
walk especially in the Moonlight it's
very nice um yeah the Bears are just
really they're really loud and it's
Sunset as well anyways
um yeah so it's mostly tied to the
season I get up very there's a tree
right next to my house and the balcony
doors
open
anyways my God so yeah um there's a
this is not
good oh my God so there's a tree next
door this is so awkward I don't like
this at
all anyways yeah so it's B of the
seasons it's based of seasons in summer
time this is
not this is not good it's not going to
be very good
so and I'm going red from laughing so in
the summertime I'm up early you know
3:00 a.m. it's light I'm up around 4:
usually on a morning walk preferably on
a run I don't run there but I want to
get into that um the questions I need to
answer
this so wake up time yeah so around
Sunrise always sunrise in the
winter around 8:30 a.m. cuz that's when
the Sun rises and it's even at 8:00 a.m.
it's groggy as [\h__\h] I just can't get up
at that time I do want to buy a huge
store light you know those like [\h__\h]
horn lights like you know really bright
to artificially make my room into some
Forest a tropical forest I flant behind
me this is my monsteria and um yes I
want this this thing called a tiger
jantis and it's this huge plant grows
very rapidly very similar to the
monsteria but it it will cover the
sealant I want to wake up to a you know
a plant above me so that's pretty cool
but obviously I need a bright light cuz
it can't exist in a [\h__\h] 6 and 1 half
hour day with zero sunlight cuz my
room's North facing but in the sun in
the summer the the sun does shine in the
North in fact it shines from so it rises
in the
Northwest sorry rises in the north east
and then sets in the
Northwest yeah so you know pretty much a
lot of coverage and even in the north so
midnight 1:00 a.m. it's still blue the
sky is always blue it's never fully
below the Horizon no kind of stars also
I'm very worried this video will be a
second there'll be two parts of this
video cuz um it says 22 minutes ver of
storage left on this phone so yeah I'm 4
minutes through so I will have to do
another video on a second device and
that's probably have better audio but
the quality of the video will be a bit
different so you'll notice that anyways
so yeah work I don't so I run so luckily
enough I live with my sister so that
helps a lot I run it's it's not illegal
but it's frowned upon so basically you
know those apps where they pay you for
your data usage or they use your phone
or a phone for their own so they'll be
able to download things they want to use
and use it for processing power so it's
like Bitcoin mining but nothing like
Bitcoin and it makes a lot more than
that anyways I have many many phones
right many many chargers there's a lot
of them and many many apps as well and
apps that SC shopping they do certain
service for Consumer programs I just
make loads of random profile files from
different people and then just just go
from there really it works for me I just
use a obviously I'm going to have to say
my age as well which I find it kind of
cringe cuz um a lot of people in the
community probably think I'm like 30 or
something I'm 21 um yeah um literally
last January January 14th that's my
birthday 2004 um and also I feel like
that's gives me a little justification
for not having a job but I'm doing my
own thing you know it it works for me
it's makes a lot and I've saved a lot so
my only worry is like if it breaks down
which last year it did one app went bust
which went for all the fs and but I had
two other apps running I've now found
another app that I can use that's three
apps running on each device yeah and it
makes usually the pays like every 3
months some apps two months some apps
one month so it's really good and
there's like panels where you can go on
calls with them but I have to be a bit
careful cuz I'm also Jenny who's 56 and
lives in Wales I'm like hello I'm from
Wales you know so I can't really do that
not illegal just R up it's the same
thing that Google Google and Facebook
get billions from our data that they
don't even fully consent to we don't
fully know what they do it's the same
thing exactly they're just paying for it
and they don't care on the wiser I've
read their terms and conditions mostly
cuz I'm freaked the [\h__\h] out if it's
illegal it's not thank God and it's so
the reason I was saying like I guess CU
I'm young I don't like that though I
hear a lot of young people going like
I'm gen C and that gives me a pass to be
a [\h__\h] loser at all not where I am
right and all these other things
clinging to youth I don't like that idea
at all I'm just saying it cuz I feel
judged by that it took a long long time
to be like yes this is what I do even
though it makes a lot of money right it
works for me I shouldn't be ashamed of
this but I am it's like uh it's not the
traditional this or that um yeah yeah so
yeah there you go um family drama
interests interest okay right so
hiking uh nature plants love
plants
um psychology I guess but not to be some
Guru like oh yes psychology yeah so deep
and interesting business my dad um he he
construction really good at handyman
type of guy so I think genetically
passed down through that business always
since I was young you know selling
things we probably look like starving
Victorian children the amount of things
I was like hey do you want to buy this
like
like there's this a jumble sale we call
them a like a yard sale but yeah jumble
is in jumble of things and it's a sale
so you sell things and yeah so we saw on
the the side of the road random things I
wanted to set up a slushy machine so a
slushy machine is probably going to be
Americans it's like a Slappy you know
the Frozen thing very nice lots of
different flavors and um I wanted to
connect a extension card from my house
cuz I live near a park and put it on the
telephone wise and just sell I never did
do that um but yeah that's one of my
little regrets I was nine but pretty
good idea if you tell me so yeah we um
charity things as well it's not really
business related but it's more like I
don't know I think it's related you know
just knocked on people's doors to do
Char who raise £50 for cancer research
rspca which is an animal protection
thing which is pretty cool I was a bit
disappointed though cuz we gave £3 to
the animal protection thing and they
just went they gave us a little
certificate it was like $29.99 I was
like why did they put that like maybe to
not be taxed or something you know if
it's a certain amount taxable
inheritance is a thing in the UK very
tax heavy but for the cancer research
one we went to a store to deposit into
those little top um pot things and they
were giving us out key rings and I was
like oh we could have got key rings so I
was like oh but this is great I want
some of this it was like I got something
from my work and I was like getting
handfuls of this you know these little
key Rings we probably took more than we
actually gave I don't know but anyways
the thought that counts the thought that
counts yeah so there's that
um yeah so family drama there's a lot um
and there's a lot that's process but
it's absent like not in touch with most
of them so it's not really a form of
drama it's not something I did it's from
when I was younger so obviously that's
you know that's a void like come on you
know 15 and age of four doesn't really
count as me being involved however yeah
there was a lot of drama a lot of drama
yeah things yeah yeah yeah let's avoid
that
one yeah um interests yeah
well improvement self-improvement that's
big although I don't do much of it I'd
like to but I I think I do I probably
do um yeah plants plants for oxygen I
really want to develop a little
ecosystem
so make my room into having double the
oxygen level that is conventional so
like just hundreds of plants to have my
own oxygen system that's just the for me
that means a lot it's NF a lot cuz it's
like hey clean air all that [\h__\h] you
know pretty cool you know mold and this
is this is also why I've got a cough I
have 65 plants this is one of them this
is on the larger size but there's bigger
ones there's a 2 me [\h__\h] Cactus over
there and right it's a winter time we
don't open the windows a lot if it's
cold outside yeah and um soil sir what
was I doing I have the plant on the
window cills right to get the most
amount of light when it's 6 and 1/ half
hour days yeah and these tropical plants
they used to around 12 hours sun above
the heart in the sky in the UK it barely
like for instance the window's like 2 m
away which is 6' 6 the wall the shadow
it hits behind me the sun does not hit
the floor it hits the walls it is
incredibly low so if you take the angle
of the sun is 90° ah head over 0° as in
on the horizon in the winter we're at
10° yeah in summer it's 60° around the
equator it's around it goes from 90 then
to 60 then 90 so yeah back s there here
we go from this all way to that back and
forth North Pole goes below the Horizon
and that's where they have 6 months of
darkness we're close we're pretty close
practic it's like a sunset Sun for six
and a half hours it's Grim it's really
depressing but we wouldn't enjoy the
summer about it so
hey right so um yeah so tell us a story
about um a week that frustrated you this
week I don't know something that
frustrated me this
week the mailman I guess the postan with
my order added more phones for the you
know the data thing and scanning your
shopping it also scanning your shopping
thing and answering surveys and stuff on
these
apps yeah it it took so long to order
eBay kept suspending my account saying
this is fraudulent like
okay cuz maybe I bought like 10 sorry
nine of the same
device it's a bit weird so
yeah that was a bit weird um what else
frustrated
me yeah that's that's all I've got
the three most closest people in your
life lovely so my sister I thought about
this as well before the questions um my
sister she's great although we fall out
sometimes like um you know and argue at
times it's not aggressive aggressive
though however my mom was um I suspect
she's a double masculine each very
intense would do the same thing there so
it's like you said this and you did that
and did and then Amnesia forget about it
5 seconds later
but hey that was 6 years ago so but yeah
anyways and there's like a bit of oh not
not really a worry of mine where like oh
that was 6 years ago oh that means that
he doesn't see his mom oh it's like a
bit annoying cuz I don't that does make
me feel cuz especially someone's
watching that I talk to a lot they don't
know this fully maybe they know about my
dad thing mention it's in passing but it
was in relation to this idea thing where
it's any yeah well mention that think it
was a bit weird
um
something oh [\h__\h] almost knocked the
thing
out I won't say that's
inappropriate right um so it was a bit a
bit annoying cuz like but I also realize
I'm an individual often think like oh
background and where you come from that
means that people have an assumption
about you but hey I am me they can take
that from space value you know so I
shouldn't be fully worried about that
but in the past there was and it took a
long long time to get over that of like
reassurance from many many people of
yet to have issues or have bad things
happen to you or to go through you
know and it's yet so my sister y so
selfless very selfless
um I would we would both be homeless if
it wasn't for her y um she's done a lot
she's done an incredible l a lot I
respect her so much she's very very
brave um although she doesn't think
it yeah I wish I had the ability to do
what she does seriously it's incredible
what she's done what she
does I don't think she even realizes how
gobsmacked of me like of her ability to
do things where I'm like I wouldn't I'm
a coward in comparison to her
seriously it's
just yeah
you know blurs my mind blurs my mind
yeah and another person firer she is
reckless she's crazy but she makes me
laugh so [\h__\h] much hilarious
extremely inappropriate we both were but
I dig her on as in like I'd make her do
it cuz it made me laugh you know not so
much now but when we were younger we'd
go into after school we'd go into like
Chinese restaurants and she go I'm dog
she's foreign herself so it's not as bad
it's not as bad cuz she's Iranian so
it's not oh the worst thing in the world
but oh I'd kind of like de go so sorry
so sorry she doesn't mean it even though
I was the one asking her to do that o
you know so yeah like lots of [\h__\h] like
that um we went to London in Co three
times yeah um she did lie about the
tickets though um we bought tickets to
Manchester this is when we were 16
during Co and she said oh I found some
for cheaper going to London um I naively
went along with it and went okay like
fine she didn't buy the tickets so we
got on the train went down to London
with our tickets spent the day there um
getting lost on the trucking I Leed the
system the tube system you know Subway
took a while took a while we got fined
cuz we didn't um tap in tap out at the
right station all that um but we managed
to talk to the people and they let us
through and then we were running for the
train but obviously two kids running
looked suspicious and also went we've
lost our tickets half us they were like
yeah [\h__\h] they didn't yep um luckily
her dad picked us up in Manchester we
got the train at 9:30 at night got there
at midnight he drove us
back um I broke down I broke down the
police we went to the police and stuff
yeah I broke down and she just went like
was I'm sobbing you
know not the best of days and we fell
out for a year after that because I was
just pissed I was extremely pissed
like she's just lied and all that you
know um yeah yeah yeah and other things
as well so like for instance I was very
helping of her like could hold out bags
and things like that and it got to the
point where it was frustrating I didn't
want to do this anymore and yeah and I
just just kind of one time I just threw
a bags on the floor not aggressively but
like just dropped them on the floor I
was like nope I'm not holding them and
they' have an issue people around
because I realized it was causing I was
causing a dependency so I was enabling
an infant type mechanism in these people
where I was a caregiver I was like a
parent and as people mature their
parents become more and more absent
because of responsibility I was fing in
that void for them without realizing it
and this person said there was this
YouTuber they said something it was like
stop causing depend people to be
dependent on you and I went wow that was
such
you know usually people say oh no don't
do this have self respect selfworth i'
find that super narcissistic what do you
mean selfworth you're putting a value on
someone what yeah I found extremely
narcissistic very toxic very worrysome
and but then I realized that yeah you do
have self Weare if you're [\h__\h] human
it's not like jeez you know been a FL
and the thingy yeah yeah so yeah and got
a bit of loop to Loop there um so I was
talking about
self wor and acceptance causing people
to have dependencies on me and I
realized I've got to cut that off I
didn't want people to depend on me at
all um so yeah that's what clicked for
me it wasn't the oh you need to do this
you have to have this and that that
didn't work for me it was you have to
stop making people dependent on you and
I was said wow so I'm kind of
manipulating them in a sense of like
doing these things for people I'm
triggering an infancy mechanism in their
brain causing this attachment where I'm
like yes this feels comforting cuz it
does if someone's doing something for
you it's a relief it's chill it's
relaxing you know holding their bags so
yeah there was that and that triggered
it and that's why we kind of broke out
cuz I finally stuck up myself it was
unusual for me to do that yeah we just
broke up and another person cuz it says
three Stella she's
um she's an interesting character she's
very aggressive she probably masculine F
Fe um I do a lot of racist jerks around
her as a jerk obviously but sometimes
too far like say there was two Polish
people and I group we were sitting
together I'd boot the chair across the
room and say we've only got we're like
we've got one of you already over there
[\h__\h] off the full we're full and then
she'd just be like oh my [\h__\h] god and
they everyone around be like what the
hell I'll be like I'm joking get up pick
a chair up and bring it back you know
you know very kind very friendly you
know it's fine it's fine just you know
it's a joke yeah so I do that and Stella
would be yeah no no no she sometimes
people would laugh other times they
wouldn't so she would be kind i' know
she'd be pissed but then she'd realized
other people were laughing so she
couldn't like Effy say anything at that
moment so I knew she was pissed it's
kind of like that but she pushed on me
she pushed on me to do things I wanted
to do so like you know um for instance
like I wanted to say something someone
was saying something [\h__\h] up to this
girl and I wanted to say something I was
like oh I really wanted she was saying
to do it do it and I was like I don't
know I don't know and other times at
school as well like you know the you
know there was like issues with like um
it was work as [\h__\h] back then I was
pretty [\h__\h] work there was gender
neutral there was no gender neutral
bathrooms yet good reason but I was
there was a head teacher in the UK it's
very traditional very strict top down
like you know so it's very intimidating
talking to the Head teacher and like um
she'd say do it do it and like she
pushed me next to and she was like s j
want to talking about something I was
like oh [\h__\h] I was like why is then
really shy why is then like this or that
and I did it you know she pushed me to
do that so I'm very grateful for doing
that but she also pushed me down the
stairs um un prompt
obviously maybe I don't know why she did
that I managed to outrun the
fall yeah um she never said why I
haven't actually spoken to her about
that but it was most but I kind of got
her back I stapped her in the leg with a
pen and during lesson she like oh no no
no no no like that so like there's just
a long history of like ever since like
we met at school like you know it
started out where she's like you know
pushed on me to better myself and stuff
and put me in uncomfortable situations
where it makes me more determined as
well now in the present and stuff which
is you know that's
good yep so what is wrong with the
government politics these days yes so
I'm very okay I've got 1 minute left on
this one so I will try and re-record
this on the next device now and leave
question four so this is part one the
part two will be coming there's probably
going to be three parts to this video
I'll link them in the playlist you don't
have to look for it it'll probably just
automatically go on the next video now
so yes see you soon imagine I'm beating
up MC
like hello I'm back